thedianerehmshow.org 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy | WAMU 88.5 - American University Radio

Protecting your privacy begins with a complete understanding of what information can be collected from you and how that information is used. Should you have any questions regarding your privacy and our policy after reading this document, please contact us for clarification at: feedback@wamu.org. You are also encouraged to review our Terms of Use.

At WAMU our relationship with you is built on trust. We're committed to preserving it.

**Information Automatically Collected**  
All webservers generate log files that record basic information about website "traffic" - what files or "pages" are requested, when they are requested, how many requests were made, what browser requested it, etc. These logs serve to help us understand how successful our site is in serving you. Our  logs do not collect personal information about you and are only reviewed to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base.

WAMU’s website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Specifically, WAMU uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, which gives us access to information that we can use to approximate our website visitors' demographics and interests. This information will be used to improve the usability of the site and deliver more relevant content. Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help WAMU analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google. Google and WAMU will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Website by disabling the Google Analytics cookie on your browser by using the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).  Also, you can manage your settings for these cookies and opt-out of this feature by updating your [Google Ads Setting](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCi2o7zseNQXNao7YVto9bKyBYr5qCex3yK-bbxh2IjQlpJbXUz4GnyGQ902ahe5sg0ytE31FDf48uBoxRuAdw8PVDaPAg).  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Information You Provide**  
Visitors to wamu.org may voluntarily supply personal information for the purpose of entering contests, when sending email, signing up for email newsletters, e-commerce transactions and conducting surveys or polls. WAMU may use this information for its own internal use solely to conduct the stated activities. In the instance when certain information is required for a particular activity it will be explicitly stated and explained at the time of submission. 

It is WAMU's policy never to sell, rent, swap, exchange, trade or make available any information we gather from you, irrespective of the manner in which we obtain this information (e.g. on-line, through direct mail, by telephone, or through direct contact).

_**Additional Information for WAMU Members/Donors**_  
A principal foundation of public broadcasting is our reliance on support from the people who rely on our programs.  Because we operate in the public interest, our future relies on a bond of public trust.  This bond extends to thousands of listeners living in hundreds of local communities of every size and description throughout WAMU’s region of service.  WAMU 88.5 cannot afford, either in appearance or in fact, to undermine that bond.  For these reasons, WAMU 88.5 certifies that is meets the following public-interest standards:

**Control:**   WAMU 88.5 will maintain active control of membership and donor lists, and takes reasonable measures to insure against unauthorized use of such lists including requiring any third party (e.g. list brokers, mailing management organizations, fundraising organizations, prospect research/data screening services, online fundraising services, telemarketing agencies, inbound telephone services, and advertising/public relations agencies) to abide by WAMU/American University’s compliance requirements.

**Privacy:**   WAMU 88.5 will respect the privacy of all subscribers and donors by offering a means by which subscribers and donors may “opt out” by contacting the WAMU Member Services office at membership@wamu.org.  Requests from WAMU members to withhold their names and contact information from solicitation by WAMU-generated letter, telephone, or electronic fundraising efforts are recorded in each individual’s donor file and honored.  Member and donor names and information are used to further the financial support of WAMU 88.5, and infrequently for confidential media research into WAMU listener trends and listening preferences. 

**Limits On Use:**   WAMU policy forbids the renting, selling, leasing, loan, trade, giving, donating, transferring, or exchanging of donor names with any other nonprofit agency. 

Per CPB requirements, WAMU 88.5 will not rent, sell, lease, loan, trade, give, donate, transfer, or exchange names to or with any candidate for public office, committees or organizations supporting a candidate, political parties, or organizations that solicit funds for use in political campaigns for any purposes whatsoever.

**Record Keeping:**   WAMU 88.5 will maintain complete and accurate records of all uses of membership and donor lists for fundraising purposes, and must furnish such records upon request to the Corporation for Public Broadcasting.  Upon your direct, personal request, we will provide you with the current information (e.g., email address, name, etc.) that we maintain about you through the most secure means available.

If you have any questions about giving or pledging your support to WAMU, or if we can be of any assistance to you, do not hesitate to contact us by e-mail to membership@wamu.org, by telephone Monday through Friday between 9 AM and 5 PM Eastern time (excluding holidays) at (202) 885-1252, or by U.S. mail to:

WAMU 88.5 FM  
American University  
4400 Massachusetts Ave., NW  
WAMU Media Center  
Washington, DC 20016-8082  
"ATTN: Member Services Dept." 

**CPB Eligibility:**   As a CPB grant-eligible public telecommunications facility, WAMU 88.5 and its licensee, American University annually certify to the CPB our continued compliance with the laws and regulations of the Internal Revenue Service, and with all other applicable federal law or regulations governing political activity and lobbying at the time of certification.  In addition, WAMU 88.5 and American University certifies continued compliance with the Control, Privacy, Regulatory Limits, and Record Keeping requirements set forth above.

**Exceptions**  
WAMU may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if WAMU believes that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with legal process, (b) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the WAMU website, or (c) protect the personal safety or property of WAMU website users, the public or WAMU and its employees.

The Internal Revenue Service may revoke the 501(c)(3) status of any organization that fails to comply with its rules, and may levy fines in the nature of excise taxes on the organization and/or its leaders who knowingly engaged in activities in violation of its rules. ** **

**Financial Information**  
All online financial transactions are processed through a secure (https://) server to ensure that any information you enter is safe.

**Links to other Sites**  
It is important to note that the WAMU website may contain links to other third party sites that may not follow the same privacy policies as the WAMU website. These sites may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that WAMU would not. WAMU is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites.

**Acceptance of This Policy**  
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the WAMU web site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at: feedback@wamu.org.  
**Last modified on: October 14, 2014**
